

Hoang Xuan Quy

Web Developer

Date of birth: 13-03-1996

Gender: Male

Phone:

Email:

Address: Ha Noi

Website:

ABOUT

With 3.5+ years of web development experience, specializing in both domestic and Japanese markets, I have extensive knowledge in developing web applications for both product and outsourcing environments. Currently, I am actively seeking full-time job opportunities in web development.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2019 UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT AND COMMUNICATIONS

Major: Engineering Languages : English B1

2018 - 2019 APTECH INTERNATIONAL IT EDUCATION SYSTEM

Main Subject: Software Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2022 - present

MOR Software SJC

Web Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Requirement Analysis
- Design and Development
- · Programming and implementation testing
- Performance Optimization
- · Maintenance and Bug Fixing
- Q&A and Communication with clients.
- Adhering to project development processes (Agile, Scrum, Waterfall).

September 2019 - May 2022

Global Technology Solutions Co., Ltd

Web Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Transferring banking domain knowledge to new team members.
- Requirement Analysis
- Design and Development
- Programming and implementation Unit Test
- Performance Optimization
- · Maintenance and Bug Fixing
- Q&A and Communication with clients.

SKILLS

Databases	- SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite, Oracle, Redis
Programing Language	- PHP, JavaScript
Framework	- BE: Laravel,Laravel Livewire, CakePHP, RESTful API - FE: VueJS ,InertiaJS,Tailwin CSS, Bootstrap
Data Visualization	- Charts, PowerBuilder
Testing	- PHPUnit ,UnitTest
Version Control	- Git, SVN
Language	English communication basicBasic level (research and technical documentation)
Other	 Documentation: writing technical documentation, user guides, and development documentation for projects (Basic design, Details design) Business Knowledge in Banking Operations (LOAN,Deposit,LC) Understanding about OOP, MVC, Design Pattern, SOLID, Dependency Injection Good understanding software design, database design Good time management, presentation and teamwork skills Understanding and experience in working with Agile development methos such as Scrum or Waterfalls.

PROJECTS

GlobalTech Solution

(September 2019 - October 2020)

Customer	Korean Credit Institutions in Vietnam (Lotte, KEB Hana, Busan)
Description	A project providing internal reporting solutions for state-owned banks in Vietnam.
Team size	7
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Receive tasks and estimated completion time Maintenance and bug fixing Develop new features Implement Unit Test Data normalization and improved query performance Create functional guides for each developed feature Communication with clients to requirements for feature development Participate in daily meetings and provided progress reports
Technologies used	PHP Laravel, Ajax, Java Script, SQL Server ,Queues job

GlobalTech Solution

(August 2021 - April 2021)

Customer	A real estate leasing corporation in Japan (Daiwa House Group)
Description	System maintenance and management for the leasing system and overall business operations of the corporation.

Team size	5
My position	Developer Backend and Frontend
My responsibilities	Performa maintenance and bug fixing Develop new features Manage batch and crontab according to schedule Synchronize data and indexed for Elasticsearch (ES)
Technologies used	Cake PHP, Ajax, jQuery, MySQL, Elasticsearch, Vagrant + VirtualBox, Docker

GlobalTech Solution

(May 2021 - May 2022)

Customer	A CRM system in Japan (CYDAS).
Description	Develop a new module within the Customer Relationship Management (CRM) system of corporation.
Team size	12
My position	Developer Backend and Frontend
My responsibilities	 Work with team leader to capture and receive requirement from customers Maintenance and fix bugs Develop features Data normalization, Improve query performance Define Test Case, Implement UnitTest with Fake data, Mocking data
Technologies used	Laravel Sanctum, RESTful APIs, Vue JS ,TailwindCSS, MySQL, Docker, AWS: SQS, S3, CI/CD

MOR Software SJC

(November 2022 - January 2023)

Customer	Hokkaido Nippon-Ham Fighters
Description	A project for managing a baseball stadium in Hokkaido, Japan.
Team size	7
My position	Developer Backend and Frontend
My responsibilities	 Daily meetings and daily reports Receive tasks and estimated completion time Built new functionalities of the web app using Laravel. Work with BrSE requirement accepted Maintenance and fix bugs Develop features Refactor code, Improve query performance
Technologies used	Laravel Livewire, Chart JS, JavaScript, MySQL

MOR Software SJC

(January 2023 - present)

Customer	A business providing survey services and advertising campaigns Japan.
Description	System for managing advertising campaigns and surveys of a Japanese business.
Team size	16
My position	Developer Backend and Frontend
My responsibilities	Daily meetings and daily reports Receive tasks and estimated completion time Maintenance and fix bug Develop new features Data normalization and improved query performance Write test cases and implemented unit tests for each deployed feature

	Create design documentation (Basic design, Detailed design) Create functional guides for each developed feature
Technologies used	Laravel, VueJS (InertiaJS), Oracle